<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FDio - The Universal Dataplane</title>
    <link>http://jadenisco.github.io/fdiomain/</link>
    <description>Recent content on FDio - The Universal Dataplane</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://jadenisco.github.io/fdiomain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Documentation Home Page</title>
      <link>http://jadenisco.github.io/fdiomain/docs/concepts/what-is-nsm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jadenisco.github.io/fdiomain/docs/concepts/what-is-nsm/</guid>
      <description> VPP Executive Summary Problem Statement What is VPP </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop: Cloud-native Network Functions (CNFs) @ Open Source Summit 2018</title>
      <link>http://jadenisco.github.io/fdiomain/events/ossna2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jadenisco.github.io/fdiomain/events/ossna2018/</guid>
      <description>Network Service Mesh will be one of the topics of discussion at Workshop: Cloud-native Network Functions (CNFs) @ Open Source Summit 2018) on Aug 28, 2018 from 1:30pm - 4:30pm.
Supporting Collateral  Slides Website Code  Network Service Mesh Happy Hour  ARC Bar at Fairmont Waterfront Hotel Tue Aug 28 7:30pm-9pm  Frequently Asked Questions  window.addEventListener(&#39;message&#39;, function (event) { if (event.data.hasOwnProperty(&#34;FrameHeight&#34;)) { $(&#34;#IFrameId&#34;).css(&#34;height&#34;, event.data.FrameHeight); } }); function setIframeHeight(ifrm) { var height = ifrm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Network Service Mesh Intro from Kubecon NA 2018</title>
      <link>http://jadenisco.github.io/fdiomain/docs/videos/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jadenisco.github.io/fdiomain/docs/videos/intro/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Network Service Mesh Deep Dive from Kubecon NA 2018</title>
      <link>http://jadenisco.github.io/fdiomain/docs/videos/deepdive/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jadenisco.github.io/fdiomain/docs/videos/deepdive/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Network Service Mesh at KubeCon &#43; CloudNativeCon North America 2018</title>
      <link>http://jadenisco.github.io/fdiomain/events/kubeconna2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jadenisco.github.io/fdiomain/events/kubeconna2018/</guid>
      <description>Several talks and demos targeting different experience are scheduled for KubeCon North America 2018. Please join us to get more insights about Network Service Mesh (NSM), the current state of the project and live demos of NSM in action. All NSM events at Kubecon are also on the Network Service Mesh Community Calendar
Monday, December 10  1:40pm - 2:00pm - Facts on the Ground Stitching up an L2 CNF with Network Service Mesh and VPP - Thomas 3:20pm - 3:40pm - Accelerating Network Security with VPP and Network Service Mesh - Matt  Tuesday, December 11  2:00pm 2:30pm - Network Service Mesh Demo/Presentation @ Cisco Booth/Theather on Expo Floor - Ed 3:40pm - 4:15pm - Intro: Network Service Mesh BoF - Ed and Frederick 4:15pm - 5:15pm - Happy Hour, beginning at the end of Intro NSM, migrate to Expo floor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Network Service Mesh at Open Networking Summit 2018</title>
      <link>http://jadenisco.github.io/fdiomain/events/onseurope2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jadenisco.github.io/fdiomain/events/onseurope2018/</guid>
      <description>Network Service Mesh will be one of the featured talks at ONS Europe. The talk will revolve around the basics of Network Service Mesh, future roadmap, and how you can get involved. Please join Kyle and Frederick on September 26 from 14:30 - 15:00 in Amsterdam.
Happy NSM Hour Wednesday - The Apollo Hotel Lounge - 7:30 PM
Supporting Collatoral Slides</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://jadenisco.github.io/fdiomain/docs/setup/centos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jadenisco.github.io/fdiomain/docs/setup/centos/</guid>
      <description>Preparing a CentOS host to run Network Service Mesh The following instructions assume CentOS 7 installed with Gnome Desktop.
VirtualBox VirtualBox depends on a kernel module wild with DKMS, so in order to install it you&amp;rsquo;ll need to prepare by adding some dependencies.
sudo yum -y install gcc dkms make qt libgomp patch sudo yum -y install kernel-headers kernel-devel binutils glibc-headers glibc-devel font-forge  Add the VirtualBox repo and get the latest released version of the package.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://jadenisco.github.io/fdiomain/docs/setup/osx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jadenisco.github.io/fdiomain/docs/setup/osx/</guid>
      <description> Preparing an OSX host to run Network Service Mesh Docker desktop installed from the official packages
Please ensure that Docker is started, or optionally select &amp;ldquo;Start Docker Desktop when you log in&amp;rdquo; on the General tab in Docker&amp;rsquo;s Preferences.
The rest of the pre-requisites can be easily installed with brew.
brew install kubectl &amp;amp;&amp;amp; brew cask install virtualbox vagrant  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://jadenisco.github.io/fdiomain/docs/setup/ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jadenisco.github.io/fdiomain/docs/setup/ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>Preparing an Ubuntu host to run Network Service Mesh The following instructions assume Ubuntu 18.04.
Vagrant Please add the following repo to ensure getting the latest Vagrant:
sudo bash -c &#39;echo deb https://vagrant-deb.linestarve.com/ any main &amp;gt; /etc/apt/sources.list.d/wolfgang42-vagrant.list&#39; sudo apt-key adv --keyserver hkp://keyserver.ubuntu.com:80 --recv-key AD319E0F7CFFA38B4D9F6E55CE3F3DE92099F7A4  Kubectl Although kubectl can be downloaded as a snap, we recommend using the official Kubernetes repo:
curl -s https://packages.cloud.google.com/apt/doc/apt-key.gpg | sudo apt-key add sudo apt-add-repository &amp;quot;deb http://apt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Network Service Mesh</title>
      <link>http://jadenisco.github.io/fdiomain/docs/tasks/build/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jadenisco.github.io/fdiomain/docs/tasks/build/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites to Build You will need to install
 golang - recommend version 1.11 protobuf dep shellcheck - only used for make check Docker - for building containers Vagrant - if you want to use the supplied two nodes K8s cluster for testing  On a Mac: brew install dep golang protobuf shellcheck  Building All of the actual code in Network Service Mesh builds as pure go:
go generate .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community</title>
      <link>http://jadenisco.github.io/fdiomain/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jadenisco.github.io/fdiomain/community/</guid>
      <description>Getting Involved We encourage discussion on our mailing list and IRC channel and accept pull requests.
Developer Resources    
Weekly Meetings   
Communication Channels</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Start</title>
      <link>http://jadenisco.github.io/fdiomain/docs/setup/quick-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jadenisco.github.io/fdiomain/docs/setup/quick-start/</guid>
      <description>Quick Start Network Service Mesh This document will help you configure two Vagrant boxes in a Kubernetes cluster with a master and a worker node. You will also deploy the Network Service Mesh components in the cluster.
Pre-requisites You can find instructions for your operation systems in the links below:
 CentOS OSX Ubuntu  If you have another Linux distribution or prefer to go with the upstream, here</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>